

ORANEKWU GABRIEL EKENE

CURRICULUM VITAE

I am a mobile application developer with 3 years of experience in Android and iOS mobile development.

I am always open to learning better ways of getting work(s) done.

Proven ability to transform client ideas into beautiful, functional design solutions.

CONTACT

+234 803 4339 010

gabrieloranekwu@gmail.com

(m) linkedin.com/in/gabbygreat



https://github.com/gabbygreat



🖊 <u>https://linktr.ee/gabbygreat</u>

EDUCATION

June 2018 till date

B Eng., Electrical Engineering Nnamdi Azikiwe University, Anambra State.

EXPERIENCE

May 2022 till date

<u>Vigoplace</u>

Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

FindMe business

Nov 2022 till date

The Pake group

PERSONAL PROJECTS

<u>IgboApp</u>

Igbo Calendar

Math App

SKILLS

Mobile App development: Dart (Flutter)

Graphic Design (Figma)

Web design (HTML and CSS)

Version Control (Git and Github)

Firebase

Postman (API Integration)

Other Programming languages Python, JavaScript